盖比
Gabe.
盖比  我有事要告诉你
Gabe, I have something to tell you.
明天我开车送你上学后
Tomorrow when I take you to school, I'm
接着我也会去学校
going to park the car and come inside.
老妈  这没得商量
Mom, we've been over this.
如果你要用洗手间  你可以去加油站的
If you have to use the bathroom, you can just go at the gas station.
你还没让我说完呢
You didn't let me finish.
你想错了  我去学校的原因是
No. The reason I'm going inside is...
请不要反应太大
Please don't freak out.
我将成为你们的校园护士
I'm gonna be your school nurse.
什么
What?!
不会吧
No!
你不能
You can't...
你为什么要这样对我
Why do you hate me?!
还好  谢谢你反应没那么强烈
Well, thank you for not freaking out.
我妈要在我学校工作
My mom is working at my school?
我完了
My life is over.
就一星期而已  不用这样吧
It's just for a week, okay?
我只是临时给你们的校园护士代一下班  她度假去了
I'm just filling in while your regular nurse is on vacation.
你为什么偏偏选中这个时候
You couldn't have done this at a worse time.
现在在学校  别人都认为我很酷
Right now at school, I'm considered cool.
我简直
I just...
好吧  看来你在说真的
Okay, you're serious.
你继续
Go on.
跟你说  有个很酷的学生叫步行者
Well, there's this really cool kid, Walker,
他邀请我和他同桌进餐
and he invited me to eat at his lunch table.
他们都是八年级的学生  我是唯一一个七年级学生
Now, they're all eighth graders, and I'm only a seventh grader.
你知道那是多大的荣耀吗
Do you how big of an honor that is?
呃  盖比  对不起  我  我不知道
Oh, Gabe. I'm sorry. I... I had no idea.
你为什么不早告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
我正好少花点钱在买食品上
I'll just turn down the money we need for groceries.
谢谢
Thank you.
然后我会教你如何讽刺人
And then I'll teach you about sarcasm.
好了  最低要求  你能不能不要告诉任何人你是我妈
Well, can't you at least not tell anybody you're my mom?
我的意思是  或许你可以换个名字
I mean, maybe you can use a different name.
嗯  我想我可以用我的娘家姓
Well, I guess I could use my maiden name.
布兰根琥珀
Blankenhooper.
很好  还有  如果我们在学校看见对方
That's good. And if we see each other at school,
我们只管走自己的路
we just keep going.
我们不交谈  不朝彼此看  反正就是不做任何交流
We don't talk, we don't look at each other, we don't interact in any way.
-那就跟我们吃早餐时的情形一样喽  -非常正确
- So just like breakfast?  - Exactly.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late and dad jokes.</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： Focus
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud.</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof.</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I survived.</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice.</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy.</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby,</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe.</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right.</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down.</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around.</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十七集
Good Luck Charlie  03x17  Nurse Blankenhooper
－嘿  老爸  －嘿  宝贝
- Hey, dad.  - Hey, honey.
噢  嘿  我是鲍伯  泰迪的老爸
Oh, hey. I'm Bob. I'm Teddy's dad.
我知道  我叫翁妮  我们见过  好像有三次了吧
I know. I'm Vonnie. We've met, like, three times.
哦  不好意思
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
没事儿  习以为常了
That's okay. Happens all the time.
有些人只是在人群中不显眼
Some people just don't stand out in a crowd.
即使是在两个人中
Or in a group of two.
嗯  我再不会忘记你的
Well, I won't forget you again.
好了  姑娘们  你们准备忙什么
All right, girls. So what you working on?
呃  就是  就是一份市场营销课的作业
Oh, it's a... it's an assignment for our business and marketing class.
大致要求是  构思出一种新产品
Basically, come up with a product idea
然后把它推销给全组成员
then pitch it to the group.
哦  懂了  我想到了一样好产品
Oh! I got... I got a good idea for a product.
让我猜猜  是食用时能清洁牙齿的玉米片
Let me guess, it's the corn chips that clean your teeth while you eat them?
我提过它们还有不同口味吗
Did I mention they come in different flavors?
再见吧  老爸
Bye, dad.
－新产品就叫洁牙玉米片  －再见啦  老爸
- Dentitos.  - Bye, dad.
我们来讨论吧
So, let's talk.
来讲讲各自的想法吧
Let's talk ideas.
－你声音怎么了  －哦  只是有点沙哑而已
- What's up with your voice?  - Oh, it's just a little scratchy.
－呃  嗯  你想到什么主意了  －这在你家  你先说吧
- So, uh, what'd you come up with?  - It's your house, you go first.
好吧  呃  我想到的新产品就是能用来跳摇摆舞的睡衣
Okay. Um, so my idea is pajamas with a fun twist.
大致是这样的  它们是一种你可以自己涂鸦装饰的连袜装睡衣
Basically, they're footie pajamas that you decorate yourself.
这是配图介绍
Introducing...
涂鸦连袜睡衣
Graffooties!
哇噢
Wow.
天啦  真是太奇怪了
Man, that is so weird.
什么太奇怪了
What is?
我和你的想法一模一样
I had the exact same idea.
我的意思是  我只是没有画出来  也没给它取名字
I mean, I don't have a drawing, or like a name,
其余的全都和你想的一样
but everything else, exactly the same.
你什么都没想  是不是
You don't have an idea, do you?
没有  女长官  我没想过
No, ma'am. I do not.
－翁妮  －怎么啦
- Vonnie?  - Yep?
这一星期来你都在做什么
What have you been doing all week?
庆幸我把你选作搭档
Congratulating myself for picking you as my partner?
来了
I'm coming.
就来了
I said I'm coming.
老妈  你来这儿干什么
Mom? What are you doing here?
我来这儿干什么  我要摆脱掉查莉和托比
What am I doing here? I'm dropping off Charlie and Toby.
我以为盖比才是你最想摆脱掉的孩子
I thought Gabe would be the first kid you got rid of.
PJ  我要去盖比的学校工作
PJ, I'm working at Gabe's school.
你得帮忙照看查莉和托比几天
You're gonna have to watch the little ones for a few days.
我不是在电话里都和埃米特说过吗
I thought I explained all this on the phone to Emmett.
－他没告诉你吗  －没有
- Didn't he give you the message?  - No, he didn't.
我打给他问问
I'm gonna call him.
喂
Hello?
埃米特  你是不是有什么事忘了告诉我
Emmett, did you forget to give me a message?
你妈要把孩子丢在这儿
Your mom's dropping the kids off.
－我三点半会来接他们  －她三点半会来接他们
- I'll pick them up at 3:30.  - She'll pick them up at 3:30.
嘿  宝贝  在这儿好好玩
Hey, you. Have fun.
嗯
Okay.
这是你家吗
Is this your house?
是的
Yep.
你是坏人吗
Were you bad?
你好  那个我不认识的孩子
Well, hello there, kid I don't know.
我是布兰根琥珀护士  你叫什么名字
I'm nurse Blankenhooper, what's your name?
你答应过不和我讲话的
You promised you wouldn't talk to me.
呃  我只是想提醒你拉链没拉上
Well, I just wanted to let you know that your zipper is down.
噢  逗你玩呢
Oh! Made you look.
爱死中学了
I love middle school.
－嘿  昨样  －你昨样
- Hey, s'up.  - S'up.
简直不敢相信今天体育课我得一英里长跑
I can't believe I have to run the mile in P.E. today.
－我讨厌一英里长跑  －嗯  我也是
- I hate the mile.  - Yeah, me too.
跑步把我的发型全毁了
It totally ruins my hair.
像你这样酷的人不该一英里长跑
Someone as cool as you shouldn't have to run the mile.
我意思是  你叫步行者  不叫飞奔者
I mean, your name's Walker, not runner.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
不用给我操心  伙计
Don't worry about me, dude.
我没打算跑
I'm not running it.
你怎么可以不用跑呢
How are you gonna get out of it?
我读八年级三年了  还是学到了点东西的
I've been in eighth grade for three years now, I've picked up some things.
噢  护士  过来一下
Oh, nurse? Over here.
怎么了
What's the problem?
噢  我刚才严重呕吐了
Oh, the problem is, I just totally barfed.
我可能上不了体育课了
Guess I can't go to P.E.
哇  那似乎是土豆汤和果汁
Wow, that looks like potato soup and fruit punch.
那正是我吃下的东西
That's what I ate.
它们大概在我胃里翻江倒海地狠斗了一番
Guess they had a fight in my stomach.
你确定它们到你胃里溜达过
Are you sure they were ever in your stomach?
地上的两滩似乎是分开的
They seem to have landed in two separate puddles.
呃  不是很明显  哈
Yeah. Gnarly, huh?
那么  你是不是该给我开张病假条让我免上体育课
So, guess you'd better write me a note to get out of P.E.
我想是的
Yeah, I better.
嗯
Okay.
我要给你开一张ID 10-T假条
I'm gonna write you an ID 10-T form.
好
Okay.
我希望你整天把这个贴在身上
I want you to wear this all day.
（白痴）
还是乖乖上体育课去吧
Enjoy P.E.
嘿
Hey...
是你啊
There she is!
There he is.
那个不记得我名字的家伙
The guy who can't remember my name.
我记得你名字
I remember your name...
科妮
Connie.
错
Nope.
呃  嗯
Oh, uh...
呃  出了点小状况  泰迪咽喉发炎了
Little bit of bad news, Teddy's got some laryngitis.
医生说她接下来几天不宜讲话
Doctor's said she shouldn't speak for a couple of days.
几天  那我们的产品介绍怎么办
A couple days? But what about our presentation?
（由你来讲）
啊  我来讲
Oh, me?
不行  我做不了
No. I can't.
（你可以的）
不行  我从来都没做过产品介绍
No, but... I've never given a presentation before.
（我会帮你）
哇  看这个
Wow. Look at this!
似乎你要说什么她全知道
It's like she knows exactly what you're gonna say.
嘿  我肯定你没为我准备卡片
Hey, I bet you don't have a card for me.
（出去）
那我还是走吧
And away I go.
噢  呃  再见
Oh, uh, good-bye...
翁妮
Vonnie!
能把这张卡片给我吗
Can I... can I keep the card?
好了  到了
Okay, here we go.
现在能把我的气球还给我吗
Can I have my balloon back now?
随便
Whatever.
－嗨  PJ  －嘿  曼迪
- Hi, PJ.  - Hey, Mindy.
没想到你在帮人照看小孩
I didn't know you were a babysitter.
没有  我只是在照看我的弟弟妹妹
I'm not. I'm just watching my brother and sister.
事实上  我现在有点为难  我家的保姆刚辞退了
Actually, I'm kind of in a bind. My nanny just canceled.
你能帮忙照看下这对双胞胎吗  就几个小时
Any chance you could watch the twins for a couple of hours?
呃  说不准
Oh... I don't know.
每小时我付你十五美元
I'll pay you 15 bucks an hour.
－每小时每个孩子十五美元吗  －当然了
- Per kid?  - Sure.
哇噢
Wow.
让我算算  那就是十五乘以二  再乘以二
Let's see, that's 15 bucks an hour times two kids for two hours.
噢  让我想下  进一
Oh, let's see. Carry the one...
答应了吧
Just say yes.
好
Yes.
好了  我的新计划是这样的
Okay. So here's my new plan.
昨天假装呕吐给倒在了地上
Yesterday's fake puke went on the floor,
明天的将会吐到布兰根琥珀护士全身
tomorrow's is gonna go all over nurse Blankenhooper.
你要往她身上吐
You're gonna puke on her?
那样是不是有点过激
Doesn't that seem a little extreme?
是
Yeah.
我们狠狠地羞辱她一番
We're gonna humiliate her so bad,
她就在学校待不下去了
she'll never show her face in this school again.
呃  后面部分我倒喜欢
Well, I do like that part.
嘿  泰迪  感觉怎么样
Hey, Teddy. How you feeling?
相当不错而且越来越好
Super good and getting better.
这是什么
What's all this?
我今天就靠这个跟你讲话了
This is how I'm going to communicate with you today.
一个把文本转换成语音的程序
A text-to-speech program.
哦
Okay.
这是产品介绍的稿子
Here's the presentation.
把它大声读出来
Read this out loud.
嗨  我是翁妮
Hi. I'm Vonnie.
今天我和我的搭档泰迪有非常激动人心的事要和你们分享
My partner Teddy and I have something very exciting to share with you today.
表现得更兴奋点
Be more excited.
让我听到你具有煽动性的声音
Give me some sizzle with that steak.
嗨  我是翁妮
Hi! I'm Vonnie.
今天我和我的搭档泰迪有非常激动人心的事要和你们分享
My partner Teddy and I have something very exciting to share with you!
停  你想要我的命啊
Stop. You're killing me.
喂  别用那种语气和我说话
Hey. Don't take that tone with me.
我只能用这种语气说话
This is the only tone I have.
我做不了  我们放弃吧
I can't do this. Let's just give up.
没毛病吧你
What is wrong with you?
你是个窝囊废吗
Are you a loser?
嘿  我不是窝囊废  你才是窝囊废
Hey! I'm not a loser! You're a loser!
就要这样
That's it.
把这种激情带到明天的产品介绍上
Use that passion tomorrow.
你会成功的  科妮
You'll nail it, Connie.
不好意思  打错了
Sorry, typo.
翁妮
Vonnie.
小可爱孩子照看服务贴心照看你的孩子始于
Little Lambs Babysitting Service, taking good care of your kids since...
昨天
Yesterday.
当然了  我们肯定有驾照啊  我已经有两年驾龄
Yes, we are fully licensed. I've been driving for two years.
（注：执照与驾照同为一词）
喂
Hello?
PJ  照看孩子太有赚头了
PJ, this babysitting thing is a gold mine.
我知道  伙计  我们照看着七个呢
I know, dude. We got seven kids.
七乘以十五  再乘以二
Seven times 15, times two...
进三  呃
Carry the three... uh.
我好无聊
I'm bored.
嗯  我也觉得无聊
Hey, I'm kinda bored too.
好吧  呃  来听音乐怎么样
Okay. Uh, how about music time?
嗯  听音乐  嗯
- Yeah, music time?  - Yeah.
－来吧  孩子们  快  －围过来  小可爱们
- Come on, kids. Yay!  - Gather around, little lambs.
－好的  －我们开始喽
- Come on.  - There we go.
呃
Uh.
拿起画笔
<i>Grab a crayon.</i>
画一朵花
<i>Draw a flower.</i>
做了这些每小时就有十五美元
<i>You get all this for 15 an hour.</i>
蹦蹦跳跳多欢喜
<i>Fun in leaps, and fun in bounds.</i>
现在来唱关于声音的歌吧
<i>And now it's time to sing about sounds.</i>
-汽车的响声是  -嘟嘟
<i>- A car goes...- Beep.</i>
-小狗的叫声是  -汪汪
<i>- And a dog goes...- Woof.</i>
-小鸟的叫声是  -啾啾
<i>- And a bird goes...- Tweet.</i>
-电话的响声是  -铃铃
<i>- And a phone goes...- Ring.</i>
-蜜蜂的叫声是  -嗡嗡
<i>- And a bee goes...- Buzz.</i>
这些就是各种叫声的拟声
<i>And these are the sounds of the sounds.</i>
<i>And these are the sounds, of the sounds.</i>
-耶  -哇噢
- Yay!  - Woo!
等等  嘘  嘘  嘘  嘘
Wait. Shh shh shh shh.
－里面在搞什么  －是女房东  呃
- What's going on in there?  - It's the landlady. Um...
嘿  孩子们  我们去洗手间考察探密怎么样
Hey, kids. How about a field trip to bathroom land?
－耶  －哇噢
- Yay!  - Woo!
嘿  注意  无声考察
Hey, come on. Silent trip.
无声考察
Silent trip.
是你啊，维纳
Verna!
是谁在那吵吵闹闹
Who's making all the noise?
我听到了孩子的声音  你带孩子到这儿来了
I heard kids. You got kids in here?
没  哪有孩子  就我们俩
No. No kids. Just us.
那这些盒装果汁怎么解释  还有你们身上的短袖
Then what's with all the juice boxes? And the shirts?
我俩只是爱喝盒装果汁的小朋友
We're just two young guys who like to drink juice from boxes,
当穿着印有自己名字短袖的时候
while wearing matching shirts.
－那样很放松  －对
- It's relaxing.  - Yeah.
好吧  我希望你们不是在做什么照看孩子之类的服务
Well, I hope you're not running some kind of babysitting service.
因为那违反大楼规定
Because that is against building regulations.
照看孩子  噢  那太可笑了
Babysitting service? Oh, that's ridiculous.
没有  这儿就我和埃米特
No, it's just me and Emmett.
洗手间里有人
Somebody in your bathroom?
呃  没  那是  马桶坏了
Mm-mm, no, it's uh, the toilet's broken.
对  我们的马桶有延后冲刷的毛病
Yeah, we're having this delayed flushing issue.
真的很恼人
It's very upsetting.
我上完厕所  喜欢立马把它冲掉
When I do my business, I like it to be gone immediately.
好了  感谢来访
Well, thanks for stopping by.
我去拿工具  马上回来
I'll grab my tools and be right back.
好的
Okay.
伙计  我们该怎么办  我们得把孩子藏起来
Dude, what are we gonna do? We have to hide the kids.
是的  嗯
Okay. Um.
到窗台上去考察
Field trip to the ledge.
不行
No.
－不行  －算了
- No.  - Okay.
－嘿  老妈  －嘿
- Hey, mom.  - Hey.
哇噢
Whoa.
怎么了
What?
没什么  就是
Nothing, it's just...
你看起来有点疲倦
You look kind of tired.
什么  太可笑了  我精神好得很
What? That's ridiculous. I feel great.
今天在办公室小睡了三个小时
Took a three hour nap in the nurse's office today.
孩子们不停地敲门  我才出来的
Kids kept banging on the door, I was out.
我想明天你还是不要去学校的好
I think you should take tomorrow off.
为什么
Why?
呃  你听说过携子工作日吗
Well, you've heard of bring your kid to work day?
那么  明天就是妈妈居家日
Well, tomorrow's keep your mom at home day.
行了吧  盖比  不用搞那一套了
Come on, Gabe. You're better than that.
好吧  你待在家就是  我无计可施了
Oh, just stay home. I'm desperate.
到底怎么了
What is going on?
好吧  我正经历人生最严重的进退两难时刻
Well, I'm going through the worst dilemma of my life.
我在想是该帮你还是和酷哥们儿们为伍  然而
It's you versus being cool, and...
我也想不通我为什么竟然选择帮你
I can't believe I'm picking you.
好了  盖比  到底怎么回事
Okay, Gabe. What's going on?
好吧  这可不是我跟你说的啊  但
Well, you didn't hear this from me, but...
明天很有可能你会被步行者往身上吐秽物
There's a good chance you're getting puked on tomorrow by Walker.
我会被吐秽物  你竟然还犹豫要不要告诉我
I'm getting puked on and you struggled to tell me?
那家伙举办的派对酷毙了
This kid throws really cool parties.
－那还是我生下了你呢  －那是很久以前的事儿了
- I gave birth do you!  - That was a long time ago!
听着  算我求你  明天能不去学校吗
Look, can you please just not come to school tomorrow?
好吧  好吧  就算我明天不去
Okay. Okay, so I don't go in tomorrow.
那周四  周五怎么办
What about Thursday and Friday?
我得躲到什么时候
When does it end?
周六
Saturday.
－轻点  轻点  －好了
- Easy. Easy.  - Okay.
太完美了
Perfect.
门没锁
It's open.
我来修马桶了
Here to fix the toilet.
洗手间在那边
Bathroom's right over there.
－那东西刚才在那吗  －什么东西
- Was that there before?  - Was what there before?
那堆成山的衣服
The giant pile of clothes.
今天是洗衣日嘛
Laundry day.
对  你要像我们一样喝那么多果汁你也会有很多衣服要洗
Yeah. You drink as much juice as we do,you're gonna have a lot of laundry.
好了  你们是不是该开始洗了
Well, shouldn't you get started with your wash?
呃
Uh...
嗯  该开始了
Yes. We should.
埃米特  快  我们开始洗吧
Emmett. Come on. Let's get started.
啊  啊  啊
Aah aah aah!
你好
Hello.
原来咽喉炎是会传染的
Turns out laryngitis is contagious.
噢  不
Oh, no.
我们的产品介绍一小时后就要开始了
Our presentation is in one hour.
我们该怎么办
What are we going to do?
噢  姑娘们  怎么了
Oh, hey girls. What's up?
我有主意了
I have an idea.
我和你的主意一样
I have the same idea.
你先说
You go first.
嗨  我是泰迪
Bob: Hi. I'm Teddy.
今天我和我的搭档翁妮有非常激动人心的事要和你们分享
My partner, Vonnie and I have something very exciting to share with you today.
我俩要带你们去
We take you to a sleepover...
国内的某个地方通宵聚会
Somewhere in the U.S.A.
叮当
Ding dong.
嘿  闺蜜  谢谢你来参加通宵聚会
Hey, girl! Thanks for the sleepover.
不客气  那是好朋友该做的
No prob. That's what besties do.
我希望有什么办法能让这沉闷的派对变得有生气
I just wish there was some way we could wake up this slumber party.
现在  有了
Well now, there is.
耶  耶  耶  耶
<i>Yeah yeah yeah yeah!</i>
有了涂鸦连袜睡衣
With Graffooties!
全新的可涂鸦睡衣
The all new pajamas you can write on.
哇噢  它把女孩们最喜欢的两样东西完美联系
Wow! That combines the two things girls love best.
绘画和睡衣
Drawing and sleepwear.
现在它们合二为一  超值放送
Now together in one super fun package.
我的天啊
Omg.
它成了我永远最好的朋友
Bff.
涂鸦连袜睡衣会让你会心大笑
Graffooties will make you lol.
哈  哈  哈
Ha ha ha.
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hee hee hee.
吼  吼  吼
Ho ho ho.
涂鸦连袜睡衣
Graffooties.
它把你的睡眠变成欢娱
They make bedtime a blast.
耶  耶  耶  耶
<i>Yeah yeah yeah yeah!</i>
啊  布兰根琥珀护士来了
Ah, there's Blankenhooper.
喂  盖比  记得你该怎么做吗
Now, Gabe. Remember what to do?
嗯  我吸引她的注意力让你趁机喝一大口蘑菇汤到嘴里
Yeah. I distract her while you take a big swig of mushroom soup.
然后噗的一声
And then boom.
我正好吐在她脸上
I get her right in the face.
噢  护士
Oh, nurse?
我感觉不太舒服
I don't feel so good.
－噢  不  怎么回事  －噢  我感觉恶心反胃
- Oh, no. What's wrong?  - Oh, I feel nauseous.
噢
Oh.
护士
Nurse!
看那边  有人似乎需要医疗帮助
Look over there. Something medical looks like it's happening.
嘿  别在那搅和  孩子
Hey, don't distract me, kid.
你没看见这个男孩病得很严重吗
Can't you see that this boy here is very ill?
幸运的是  我有备而来
Fortunately, I've come prepared.
－那是什么  －给你治疗恶心的针剂
- What's that?  - Your anti-nausea shot.
啊  我不需要
Uh... I don't need it.
事实上  我现在感觉完全好多了
Actually, I'm feeling a whole lot better now.
噢  不  那证明呕吐正让你变得头脑不清
Oh, no. That means the puke is eating your brain.
我得在你脑袋上打一针
I'm gonna have to give you this shot right in your head.
－在我头上打  －是的
- In my head?  - In your head.
首先  当然了  我得剃掉你的头发
First, of course, I'm gonna have to shave your hair.
什么  不
What? No!
来吧
Here we go...
啊
Mmm!
哇噢  意大利面条
Spaghetti.
嗯  好吧  查莉  呃
Okay. All right, Charlie. Uh...
呃  泰迪仍然不能讲话  所以
Well, Teddy still can't talk so...
呃  老爸得代她拍一下视频日记
Uh, dad's gonna fill in for the video diary.
那么  呃
So, uh...
祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
怎么了  我认为那样很好啊
What? I thought that was pretty good.
那我们  好吧 那我们  好吧
We... all right. We... okay.
呃  查莉  我想我该多说几句  所以  呃
Uh, Charlie, I guess I'm supposed to say more. So uh...
好吧  呃
All right, well uh...
呃  这周呢  呃  泰迪学到了非常有用的一课
Okay, so this week, uh, Teddy learned a very valuable lesson...
关于  呃  呃
About um... uh...
做自我
Being yourself?
诚实
Telling the truth?
追逐目标
Going for it?
团队合作
Teamwork?
Teamwork!
团队合作
Teamwork.
因为  哦  哦  哦  哦
Because... oh oh oh oh!
因为如果你不配合团队工作团队就没法儿工作
Because if you don't work as a team, then the team don't work.
哈  那个怎么样
Huh? How about that.
那  行了吧  已经非常好了  我说了很多了
That... come on, that's pretty good. I got a bunch of that.
（出去）
祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
自从那次产品介绍后  我的声音就变成这样了
Ever since the presentation, my voice has been like this.
你以为就你一个人声音出现了问题
You think you got problems?
我因为这个都被踢出保龄球队了
I got kicked off my bowling team because of this.
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
很诡异的事情发生了
Something really strange is going on around here.
说来听听
Tell me about it.
我知道我处在变声期  但也不该变成我妈的声音啊
I know at this age my voice is supposed to change, but not into my mom's!
你来这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
维修马桶
I'm just here to fix the toilet.